question_data = [
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type":"boolean",
        "difficulty":"medium",
        "question":"Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.",
        "correct_answer":"True",
        "incorrect_answers":["False"]
        },
        {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The name of the main character of the video game \"The Legend of Zelda\", is Zelda.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main character in the \"Half-Life\" franchise is named Morgan Freeman.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In \"Super Mario 64\", collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In \"Mario Kart 64\", Waluigi is a playable character.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Luigi is taller than Mario?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game \"Battlefield 1\" takes place during World War I.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In \"Super Mario Bros.\", the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater was released in 1999.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In \"Portal 2\", Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: \"Justice rains from above!\"","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2005 video game \"Call of Duty 2: Big Red One\" is not available on PC.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In Undertale, having a \"Fun Value\" set to 56-57 will play the \"Wrong Number Song Call\".","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the \"Half-Life\" series, \"H.E.V\" stands for \"Hazardous Evasiveness Vest\"","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the game \"Subnautica\", a \"Spadefish\" will attack you.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the game \"Subnautica\", a \"Cave Crawler\" will attack you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are \"Oathkeeper\" and \"Oblivion\".","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In \"Undertale\", the main character of the game is Sans.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Riot Games \"League of Legends\" the name of Halloween event is called \"The Reckoning\".","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In RuneScape, one must complete the \"Dragon Slayer\" quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The ghosts in \"Pac-Man\" and \"Ms. Pac-Man\" have completely different behavior.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game \"Pocket Morty\" has a Morty called \"Pocket Mortys Morty\"?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"\"Return to Castle Wolfenstein\" was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William \"B.J.\" Blazkowicz.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The video game \"Fuel\" has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"During pre-production of \"Super Mario Bros.\", Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"In \"Minecraft\", gold tools are faster than diamond tools.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the video game \"Splatoon\", the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The game \"Jetpack Joyride\" was created by \"Redbrick Studios\".","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Paradox Interactive game \"Stellaris\" was released in 2016.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In \"Resident Evil\", only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
        ]